

## **ABOUT ME**

A Cyber Security Enthusiast, Researcher, who try to achieve highest standard possible at any given risk. Interested in exploring and making tools, scripting and do development, CTFs, Bug Hunting, Pentesting, Reverse Engineering, etc. A coffee addict and looking towards a career in Cyber Securiy and development.

#### MY CONTACT

#### **Phone:**

+91 9633 253 253

#### **Email:**

sejoynerjoy@gmail.com

## Website:

https://c0ff33b34n.github.io/

## **Address:**

Kannampilly (H), North Chalakudy; 680 307

## REFERENCE

## **Don C John**

Developer, Penetration tester Cell: +91 81369 26700

#### **Akhil Dev**

Senior Software Developer, Cell: +91 90741 23050

# **SEJOYNER JOY**

## PENTESTER

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Security Researcher at Intigriti and many VDPs**

- Reported bugs and vulnerabilities in different platforms, mainly RedBull.
- Reported bugs and vulnerabilities in different platforms, also HOF at United Nations, inflectra.com

#### **IEEE Volunteer**

Web Master, LINK Representative

May 2018 - till date

- Active IEEE volunteer.
- Participated and organized many IEEE events.

## **Cyber Security Analyst at Industrus Tech**

Security Analyst, Penetration tester, Developer Sept 2021 - till date

- Secured many websites
- Trained 500+ students on web security

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### **HackTheBox**

- Got Rank: 300 all over the world.
- Got different badges.

### **HackerRank**

• Got Rank: 1 all over the world in Python.

#### Intigriti

• Got Rank: 280 all over the world and got many private invitations.

### **SKILLS AND HOBBIES**

- # Pentesting (Mainly Web)
- # Dorking
- # Linux
- # Burp Suite
- # Reverse Engineering
- # Researching
- # CTFs
- # Bug Hunting
- # Python, Bash
- # HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- # Teaching

#### **EDUCATIONAL TRAINING**

## Sahrdaya Collage of Engineering and Technology

B-Tech in Computer Science

- Enrolled since Sept. 2018 to present
- Taking up specialization courses in cyber security to broaden skill set.

#### St. Joseph's EMHSS Aloor

Plus two Computer Science

- Enrolled since July 2016 to 2018
- First step in Computer Science.